(Leonard:)Okay, we need to talk.
(Sheldon:)About what?
(Leonard:)Cats, Sheldon.
(Leonard:)You're clearly upset
about Amy being gone,
(Leonard:)and you're trying to replace
her with a bunch of cats.
Clowder. What?
(Sheldon:)A group of cats is a clowder.
Or a glaring.
(Leonard:)Okay, yeah, fine.
(Sheldon:)It's the kind of thing you ought
(Sheldon:)to know now that we have one.
Terrific. My point is,
you need to face up
(Leonard:)to what you're feeling
with this breakup.
(Sheldon:)It wasn't a breakup.
(Sheldon:)A breakup would imply that
Amy was my girlfriend.
Okay, I got it, I got it;
she's not your girlfriend.
(Leonard:)Now listen to me.
(Leonard:)I know about loneliness.
(Leonard:)I know about trying to replace
someone with other stuff.
(Leonard:)When I broke up with Penny,
I got back into my cello,
(Leonard:)I built a bunch of model rockets,
(Leonard:)I got those weightlifting gloves
and that five-pound dumbbell.
(Sheldon:)You didn't break up,
she dumped you.
(Leonard:)She didn't dump me.
(Leonard:)It was mutual!
(Sheldon:)I was there. She dumped you.
(Leonard:)Okay, fine.
(Leonard:)Live with cats.